A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1966-1967
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Files, 1966-1967
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Southern Fellowships Fund (see also Council of Southern Universities) 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Southern REGIONAL Education Board 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Southern University Conference 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Space Science, Division of 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Space Utilization 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech and Drama 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speeches 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Graduate Education: Key to the Future, Governor's Conference on Education - 5 October 1966 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - The Vision of "University"- 15 November 1966 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Norfolk Rotary Club, 6 December 1966 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Virginia Student Aid Foundation, 14 January 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Education Writers - 18-19 January 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Wilmington Alumni, 16 March 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Inauguration of President Herbur of Jefferson Medical College, 3 May 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Alumni Day Luncheon, 6 May 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - ODK luncheon, 11 May 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Speech - Final Day, 4 June 1967 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - State Board for Community Colleges 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - State Board of Education 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - State Department of Education 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - State Technical Services Act 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - State Universities Association 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - Student Affairs 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Student Council 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Student Costs 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Student Health Department 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Student Legal Forum 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Student Placement 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Summer Session, 1966 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Summer Session - Finals, 1966 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Summer Session, 1967 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 46)
  - Traffic Control 1966-1967 (Box 47)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 47)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) 1966-1967 (Box 47)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - U. S. Department of Defense 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (H. E. W.) 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - University Center in Virginia 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - University Hall 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - University Houses 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - University Houses - Faulkner 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - University Press of Virginia 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - Universities RESEARCH Association 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - Upward Bound 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 48)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia Colonial Records Project 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia Commission on Higher Educational Facilities 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia Education Association 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - General 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Blandy Farm 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Board Committee 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Buildings and Grounds Committee 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Educational Policy Committee 1966-1967 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Executive Committee 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Finance Committee 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Mary Washington College Committee 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Medical Committee 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Organization (Admin.) of the University 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Recognition of Benefactors of the University of Virginia, Special Committee 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Docket, 7 October 1966 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 7 October 1966 1966-1967 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Docket, 10 December 1966 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 10 December 1966 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Docket, 18 February 1967 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 18 February 1967 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Docket, 8 April 1967 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 8 April 1967 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Docket, 2 June 1967 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 2 June 1967 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - "W - Wh" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 52)
  - "Wi -Wz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 52)
  - Walpole Society 1966-1967 (Box 52)
  - Walter Reed - Yellow Fever Archive 1966-1967 (Box 52)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1966-1967 (Box 53)
  - Water Pollution Control Laboratory 1966-1967 (Box 53)
  - Water Resources 1966-1967 (Box 53)
  - Wheeler-Bennett, Sir John 1966-1967 (Box 53)
  - Women, Dean of 1966-1967 (Box 53)
  - "X-Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 53)
  - YMCA 1966-1967 (Box 53)